(Kim Kang Min plays Choi Si Yeol)
(Park Jin Woo plays Na Aijun)
(Byung Hun as Yeon Joo Ha)
(Kim Hongjun plays Ji Kyusung)
("My idol is chasing me?!")
(4 hours before the incident)
What I told you
are you still thinking about it
I'm to you...
very interested
If you already have…
If you are dating someone
I don’t have anyone to date
Really shameless
great
No need to pick up the red wine glass
Hold it with your fingers like this
good
Teacher Luo
are you okay
It's better to end here today.
It's time for us to go
I'll take you home
OK
Let's go
thank you
I didn't know there was construction on the road, so I took a detour.
Can you wait for me for 5 minutes?
ok no problem
Goodbye
Teacher Luo
Teacher Luo Aijun
-Teacher Luo, where is your home? -What are you doing?
Why do you keep calling me teacher?
what
No, aren't you flirting with me?
are you serious
serious
Of course you are serious
In this case, you should change the title of teacher.
Calling me teacher feels like our relationship is very distant.
After every sentence, call me Teacher Luo
People as dreamy as you keep coming closer to me
I don't even know
Is this a dream or reality?
I can't believe you're here with me
Really happy...
unbelievable
I really hope that when I open my eyes tomorrow
Just don't disappear
So…
Do you want to stay with me today?
When you open your eyes tomorrow
I will also stay by your side
(Episode 5: I obviously came close to you on purpose. How could it be...)
I really hope that when I open my eyes tomorrow
Just don't disappear
So…
Do you want to stay with me today?
It’s a dream again
Why do you keep appearing in my dreams?
upsetting
Why have you always…
After that, the whole fragment
Luo Aijun, go to hell
I can’t even tell if it’s a dream or reality.
How dare you kiss Shi Yeol?
I know you are awake
After brushing your teeth and washing your face, let's have breakfast.
I…
He actually showed up at Shi Lie’s house
The house I see every time on the live broadcast
My agent said
Come up to my house now
Now?
He called me at my door
Then what?
I told him I would be downstairs in 10 minutes and sent him away first.
so good
Take a seat
Have a full meal before going to work
It's okay, I don't need breakfast
This seems to be causing you trouble. I'll leave first.
Mr. Shi Lie Yesterday...
Shi Lie
clam
Didn’t you call me Shi Lie yesterday?
Luo Aijun, you really have all kinds of talents.
I'm so rude to you
sorry
No way
I prefer you to call me by my first name
There is still time anyway
Eat before you go to work
You know you have to shoot today, right?
See you at school later
Thank you…
I'll leave first
Right
There is a contact named 'Kui Kui'
Call you
Ah…
I don’t know if he is worried about you because he keeps calling you.
I originally wanted to say whether I should answer the call, but in the end I didn’t.
who is he
Let me see if you use this nickname to save as a contact name
You should be familiar with each other
Now this situation
If you say it directly...
He is my roommate
Actually you know him too
His name is Ji Kyu Sung
Is Ji Kyu Sung?
Are you talking about Director Chi of our company?
Yes
He and I are cousins
I'm temporarily staying at his house
So you've been hiding this all this time?
I didn't hide it
Put it this way
You know Director Chi, but you don’t know A-One
It's totally unreasonable
Wait
Did you also lie to me when you said you didn't know me at school?
I didn't lie to you
Actually…
I'm your fan
You are even my fan
wow
Wait
So...you come to my house when you're drunk
Were these all done to get closer to me?
No
Not like that
where are you touching
you make me very uncomfortable
makes me feel flustered
I feel very uncomfortable
Si Yeol, I’m sorry.
Wait, listen to me first, okay?
Stay away from me
(The above are all adapted from Aijun’s mind
Si Yeol wouldn’t speak in this tone^^)
Ha, really
That's my nephew
He keeps begging me to give him pocket money
So that's it
I'm leaving first
See you later
Brother Aijun
Brother Aijun…
Right
Dear Shi Lie...
Oh, I saw this during Shi Yeol’s live broadcast
Don't touch it casually
How can he be so sexy inside and out?
How can he still be so gentle and kind?
He even visited Shi Lie’s house
You are so lucky, Luo Aijun
(Super strong pursuit: Super strong star chasing luck(?))
It's basically 'chasing super strength'
Damn it
That photo
This is a behind-the-scenes photo of our Shilie 2024 spring and summer series.
So handsome
what is this
Wait
Could this be...
Hickey?
(There are 7 days left for the final exam)
Can you see it?
You can see it a little bit
boy
Don’t you know that you are not allowed to enter the Academic Affairs Office during the test period?
What year and class are you in...
Teacher Luo Aijun
Teacher Luo, why are you wearing sportswear?
Because I seem to have symptoms of a cold and a sore throat...
So I temporarily borrowed them from students to wear.
Then why don't you wear a scarf?
Anyway, you are really strange
When will he come?
Hello
2 3
-Hello, senior. -Hello, senior.
Hello, are you here to watch?
Yes, let’s watch EZ-senpai’s performance
Okay, keep up the good work
Thank you, senior
-See you next time -Goodbye, senior
Where are you going later?
Hello…
Hey, did you hear that?
- I heard it. - He told me to see you next time.
He didn't tell you, he told me
No, he's that tall
It's so noisy, come here
Brother, do you want to read the report?
Reports on the follow-up song
- So fast? - Yes
Was it a good shot?
Yeah, this photo is nice
-I think this one looks good. -Yeah
It’s Si Yeol…
Hello I am your big fan
Please sign your name for me
Can I take a photo with you? I'm really your fan.
- He signed it. - Don't stay around.
The name is…
-Luhe -No, this is mine
Min Yiqi
-Write the date too. -I love you.
You know you're handsome, right?
-You are so handsome. -Thank you.
-Why is your head so small? -Thank you.
Wait, can we see your abs?
- I'll just touch it once. Please - I'm sorry.
Wait, I just want you to take a look at it.
Anyway, when you get older, you won’t be able to do anything anymore.
What are you still doing now?
Hey, he will hear it
I just want to tell him.
When will my Dojun come out?
Yeah
Hello
Run quickly
Forget it, we're going to be late
Do they have any tutors?
Brother, just pretend you didn’t hear it.
Singing is not important
You can sell out just by your face.
-He looks so handsome. -He has a great figure.
(Hello, I am Ji Kyusung, the manager of IMZ Entertainment.
Actors who signed up to audition for Director Bai's film...)
Hello Producer
I'm about to send it to him now
good
OK thank you
(Lianzhu River)
(9 months ago)
If you start shooting from early in the morning later, you will probably be very tired.
I even let you go home
Don't
If you don’t take time out while moving
How can I have time to play?
Ji Kuisheng
When can I go on a date with you?
It's cold
Let me cover you with this. It's very cold.
I really hope my legs never get better
So that you can always stay by my side
Hey, what kind of joke are you kidding?
I'm not kidding
So you can't abandon me
Never
Oh, it's true
Anyway, your words are too big
It made me jump with fear
Is this just about talking?
The scale of physical contact is also very large.
Really
come here
Ji Kuisheng
Yeah
i love you
how much love
so hungry
teacher
Not to mention spare clothes
You don’t even have a set of clothes today?
Why are you doing this to me?
I didn't mean it
I have my own reasons. I'm really sorry.
There's nothing we can do about it
I'll join in the middle later.
Lines introducing student uniforms and sportswear...
I can speak my lines well
you don't have to worry
Shi Lie, you’re here
Si Yeol is here and the set-up begins.
-Okay -Okay
Then we'll give a signal later
As for the lines...
Otherwise, let's do this
How about taking this opportunity to wear couple clothes?
Couple outfit…
This is the school uniform
I think it goes well with the theme of today's program. How about it?
No problem
Yeah
If there's no problem, go change clothes.
Shooting will start in 20 minutes
OK I got it
Wow...no
Wow, your school uniform looks good too.
Right
The staff asked me to leave it to you
(Choi Si Yeol)
Please help me pin it
Me?
good
Smell my shampoo scent from someone else
Feeling so strange
OK
Right
Let’s talk about our photos
I said I wanted to shoot it before, but I haven’t done it yet.
You seemed very busy then
Can you please take a photo now?
Give it to me, I'll take the photo
A little more
If you get closer
I feel like he'll take the bait
The photo seems to have been taken very well
("Pure Love (Siyeol SOLO)")
Ah this...
Because I saw this song appeared on the news homepage
Are you interested in me now too?
No
Wha...what
Not like that
I always listen to your songs
The follow-up song is very nice
Especially the lyrics are particularly beautiful
Your previous songs and this song
Because of this filming, I listened to it all from the beginning.
The lyrics you write are kind of...
touching feeling
I got a lot of comfort
So strange
Wait, can we see your abs?
Anyway, when you get older, you won’t be able to do anything anymore.
What are you still doing now?
Hey, he will hear it
Singing is not important
You can sell out just by your face.
-He looks so handsome. -He has a great figure.
It was obvious that I flirted with him on purpose
-Why... -Thank you
Wrote so many good songs
Why do I get comfort from him?
"My idol is chasing me?!"
So what's your answer?
Are you willing to date me?
Well I do
You don't have to give it to me
Can couples do this?
Have a good dream
So you have to keep the matter of you living with me a secret.
Do you want to come to my house after work?
I was in a hurry to send you away and felt it was a pity
can you bear it today